ILGWU Education Department Publications 5780/166 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Brother Can You Spare a Finger., Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Brother Can You Spare a Finger., Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Flyer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: You Can't Eat an Average., Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Where's My Raise, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Central Classes., 1955-1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  2 copies
  - Item 1: Central Classes., Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    By Education Department. Flyer. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. The Church and Unionism., Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Church and Unionism., Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Clippings., 1920-1921; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  English and Yiddish. January 1920-March 1921. Photocopies.
  - Item 1: Clippings., Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    By Education Department. January 1920-March 1921. Photocopies. Item is in English; Yiddish.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Conversion of War to Peacetime Economy., 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  March 1944.
  - Item 1: Conversion of War to Peacetime Economy When Our Fighting Men Return., Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    By Education Department. March 1944. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Day-by-Day at the First Midwest Region Institute., 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Day-by-Day at the First Midwest Region Institute., Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    By Education Department. School For Workers, University of Wisconsin, June 23-30, 1951. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Equal Opportunity Union Made., 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Equal Opportunity Union Made., Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    By Education Department. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Everybody Sings., 1942; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  May 1942. Photocopy.
  - Item 1: Everybody Sings., Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    By Education Department. May 1942. Photocopy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Facing the Future., 1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  March 1945. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Facing the Future: Where Do We Go From Here., Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    By Education Department. March 3, 1945. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Fifty Years of I.L.G.W.U. History (1900-1950), Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  I.L.G.W.U. Filmstrip no.4. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Fifty Years of I.L.G.W.U. History (1900-1950), Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    By Education Department. I.L.G.W.U. Filmstrip no.4. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Growing Up 1917-1938., Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Growing Up 1917-1938., Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    By Education Department. 21 Years of Education With the ILGWU. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Handbook of Trade Union Methods., 1937-1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  1937 edition and 1948 edition.
  - Item 1: Handbook of Trade Union Methods., Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    By Education Department. With Special Reference to the Garment Trades. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Handbook of Trade Union Methods., Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. History of I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Syllabus for Officers' Qualification Course. Lessons 1-6. [Lesson 5 mis- labeled as Lesson 6]
  - Item 1: History of I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    By Education Department. Syllabus for Officers' Qualification Course. Lessons 1-6. [Lesson 5 mis- labeled as Lesson 6]. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. How to Conduct a Union Meeting., 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  3 copies.
  - Item 1: How to Conduct a Union Meeting., Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    By Education Department. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. I. L.G.W.U. Film Catalogue., Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: I. L.G.W.U. Film Catalogue., Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. I.L.G.W.U. Publications., 1939-1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  Two copies of 1939 catalog and one copy each of the 1939-1940 and 1940-1941 catalogs.
  - Item 1: I.L.G.W.U. Publications., Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    By Education Department. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: I.L.G.W.U. Publications., Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: I.L.G.W.U. Publications., Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Introducing Your Union., 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Introducing Your Union., Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Know Your City., 1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Know Your City., Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    By Education Department. Our Saturday Visits to Points of Interest. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Knowledge is Power., 1927-1928; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  English and Yiddish.
  - Item 1: Knowledge is Power., Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    By Education Department. Item is in English; Yiddish.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Labor Defends Democracy., 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  September 1941.
  - Item 1: Labor Defends Democracy., Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    By Education Department. Defense Series 1, September 1941.. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Lets Go!, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  Manual for Education Committees. One copy printed 1955; one copy undated. Mastheads differ slightly between copies.
  - Item 1: Lets Go!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    By Education Department. Manual for Education Committees. One copy printed 1955; one copy undated. Mastheads differ slightly between copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Lets Sing!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Lets Sing!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. The McCarthy Balance Sheet., 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: The McCarthy Balance Sheet., Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    By Education Department. Reprinted from the New York World-Telegram and The Sun. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Must we Have a Depression?, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  January 1947. Two slightly different copies.
  - Item 1: Must we Have a Depression? What Can We Do About It? Part 2, Summary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    By Henry David. January 1947. Two slightly different copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Operation I.L.G.W.U. Education Presentation., 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  May 14, 1956.
  - Item 1: Operation I.L.G.W.U. Education., Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    By Education Department. Presentation made to Atlantic City Convention of the ILGWU, May 14, 1956. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Organized Labor and Politics as a Factor in the 1936 Election., 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  July 1937.
  - Item 1: Organized Labor and Politics as a Factor in the 1936 Election., Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    By Education Department. July 1937.. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Organizing the Peace., 1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
  May 1945.
  - Item 1: Organizing the Peace., Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    By Education Department. May 1945.. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Outline of Orientation Course for new Members., 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Outline of Orientation Course for new Members., Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    By Donna Allen. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. An Outline of Social and Political History of the United States., 1923; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
  Educational Series no.1. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: An Outline of Social and Political History of the United States., Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    By Harry J. Carman. Educational Series no.1. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Porque El Obrero Debe Votar., Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  Spanish
  - Item 1: Porque El Obrero Debe Votar., Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
    By Education Department. Reprint from Justicia. Item is in Spanish.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. [vol.1] [folder 1 of 2], Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Organized Labor and Politics as a Factor in the 1936 Election., Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Education Department. July 1937. From Publications. [vol.1] Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Publications List, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Education Department. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Adult Education Faces the Future, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Adult Education Bulletin, December, 1944. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The ILGWU Management Engineering Department, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Education Department. Training For Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Relationship Between Unions and Engineers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By William Gomberg. Reprinted from Mechanical Engineering, June, 1943. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Laborite Looks at the Business World Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By William Gomberg. Reprinted from the Bent of Tau Beta Pi, December, 1943. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A State Writes a Textbook; New York's new book on labor relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Progressive Education, December, 1943. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Story of Scapegoats in History: They Got The Blame, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Kenneth Gould. Comic book, reprinted from True Comics Magazine.. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Activities of the I.L.G.W.U. Research Department., Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Lazare Teper. Reprinted from Labor Information Bulletin, May, 1942. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Max D. Danish. Reprinted from Labor Information Bulletin, August, 1939. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Ladies' Garment Worker in History and Shop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By David Dubinsky. Reprinted from American Federationist, February, 1942. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Opportunity for Leadership, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Julius Hochman. Reprinted from The Nation, September 11, 1943. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Should Unions be Regulated by Law, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Emil Schlesinger. Training for Union Service. Resolution proposed by Committee on Labor Law, Sixty-fifth annual meeting of the New York State Bar Association, January 23, 1942. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Social Psychology for the Worker., Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Becky Chalmers Barton. Syllabus for Discussion Groups, School For Workers, University of Wisconsin, December 1940. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The 30-Hour Week in Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Item 16: Your "Price Ceiling Record", Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Item 17: Rules of Order, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By John F. Sullivan. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Church and Unionism., Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By Education Department. April, 1941. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. [vol.1] [folder 2 of 2], Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Organized Farmers and Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    By Education Department. Training for Trade Union Service. Transcript of broadcast of the National Farmers' Union Program, February 22, 1941. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Money and Banking, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 3: Labor Leaders as Speakers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    By Mark Starr. Eastern Public Speaking Conference, April 19, 1941. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labor and Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    By Mark Starr. New England Association of Teachers of Social Studies, Boston, May 6, 1944. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Defends Democracy., Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    By Education Department. Defense Series 1. September, 1941. From Publications. [vol.1] Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The I.L.G.W.U. Quiz, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    By Abe S. Weiss. November, 1939. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Government and the Worker, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 8: Garment Workers in Other Lands, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    By Abe S. Weiss. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Workers and the Arts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Music, May-June, 1945. From Publications. [vol.1]. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. vol. 2, 1921-1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
  English and Spanish.
  - Item 1: The Educational Work of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By Fannia Cohn. Report submitted to the Conference of the Workers' Education Bureau of America. From Publications. vol.2. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: An Outline of Social and Political History of the United States., Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By Harry J. Carman. Educational Series no.1. Third copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Trade Union Policies and Tactics: An Outline, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By David J. Saposs. Educational Series no.2. Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Educational and Social Activities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By Fannia Cohn. Reprinted from American Federationist, Descember, 1929. Publications. vol. 2. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Our Educational Activities, 1917-1934, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By Education Department. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Introducing Your Union., Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By Education Department. From Publications. vol. 2. Third copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Introduciendo Vuestra Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By Education Department. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 8: You and Your Union., Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Item 9: A Manual for Trade Union Speakers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By August Claessens. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The ABC of Parliamentary Law, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By August Claessens; Rebecca Jarvis. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. vol. 3, 1936-1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: The Government and the Worker, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Education Department. From Publications. vol. 3. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The ABC of Parliamentary Law, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By August Claessens; Rebecca Jarvis. From Publications. vol. 3. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Depression and After in the Women's Garment Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Education Department. Extract fro the GEB Report to the 23rd ILGWU Convention, 1937. From Publications. vol. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Women's Garment Industry: An Economic Analysis., Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Lazare Teper. From Publications. vol. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: How to Start Classes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Education Department. From Publications. vol. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Structure and Functioning of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Education Department. Revised edition. From Publications. vol. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Training for Garment Jobs., Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Leon Stein. Reprinted from Justice, October 1, 1940. From Publications. vol. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Needles and Pins., Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Ben Yomen. Cartoons, reprinted from Justice. From Publications. vol. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Twenty-Fifth Year. Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1941 to May 31, 1942. From Publications. vol. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Educational Department Launches Defense Program for New York Locals, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Education Department. Defense Series 4. January, 1942. From Publications. vol. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Train Body and Brain to Serve Your Union and Your Country: Program for New York City., Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Education Department. Flyer. From Publications. vol. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Conversion of War to Peacetime Economy When Our Fighting Men Return., Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By Education Department. March 1944. From Publications. vol. 3. Second copy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. vol. 4, 1939-1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1942 to May 31, 1944. From Publications. vol. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: She Didn't Know, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By M. A. Goldstein. December, 1944. From Publications. vol. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: There Are No Master Races!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. Comic book, reprinted from True Comics Magazine. From Publications. vol. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Facing the Future: Where Do We Go From Here., Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. March 3, 1945. From Publications. vol. 4. Third copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Workers' Education and the Social Studies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Fannia Cohn. Reprinted from Social Education, v.9:no.4 (1945:April). From Publications. vol. 4. Third copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Organizing the Peace., Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. From Publications. vol. 4. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Brigade Bugle Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. Issue no.10 (1945:June). From Publications. vol. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Bearers of Light, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. Dedicated to the 25th Anniversary of the I.L.G.W.U. Student Fellowship, November 24, 1945. From Publications. vol. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Are You Prepared for Postwar Problems? Program for New York City., Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. Flyer. From Publications. vol. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Books for a Troubled World: The Influence of Literature on Our Daily Life. The Contribution of Creative Criticism to the Enjoyment and Understanding of Good Books., Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Fannia Cohn. March 2, 1946. From Publications. vol. 4. Brown cover, third copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Books for a Troubled World: The Influence of Literature on Our Daily Life. The Contribution of Creative Criticism to the Enjoyment and Understanding of Good Books., Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Fannia Cohn. March 2, 1946. From Publications. vol. 4. Yellow cover, second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Twelfth Annual Concert, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. April 13, 1946. From Publications. vol. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: At Your Service., Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. Issues no.1-3 (1946: June-Dec.). From Publications. vol. 4. Third copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: You and the World: Learning, Playing, Action., Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. October, 1948. From Publications. vol. 4. 2 copies, one brown cover and one yellow cover. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1944 to May 31, 1946. From Publications. vol. 4. Third copy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. vol. 5, 1944-1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Must we Have a Depression? What Can We Do About It? Part 1., Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Fannia Cohn. January, 1947. From Publications. vol. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Must we Have a Depression? What Can We Do About It? Part 2, Summary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Henry David. January, 1947. From Publications. vol. 5. Third copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Arts in a Troubled World. Part 1., Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Education Department. May 3, 1947. From Publications. vol. 5. Third copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Arts in a Troubled World. Part 2, Summary., Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Henry David. May 3, 1947. From Publications. vol. 5. Third copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Unions and the Community, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Fannia Cohn. From Publications. vol. 5. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Story of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Max D. Danish; Bernard Seaman. From Publications. vol. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Short Course in Parliamentary Procedure, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Education Department. From Publications. vol. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Education for a Troubled World. Part 1., Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Education Department. February 28, 1948. From Publications. vol. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Education for a Troubled World. Part 2, Summary., Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Henry David. February 28, 1948. From Publications. vol. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: You and the World: Learn, Play, Act., Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Item 11: Who Makes Public Opinion? Part 1., Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    By Fannia Cohn. March 26, 1949. From Publications. vol. 5. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. vol. 6, 1946-1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Impartial Machinery in the Dress Industry., Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Harry Uviller. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1948 to May 31, 1950. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor's National Hero, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By J. C. Rich. Reprinted from Liberty Magazine, May, 1950. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Everybody Sings., Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Education Department. March, 1951. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.